online-downloader.com 2016-11-06

# Privacy Policy - Free Online YouTube Convert and Download, YouTube MP3, YouTube Video, Download YouTube, Online Download YouTube, Online YouTube Download, , Online YouTube Downloader, YouTube Converter, YouTube Convert, Free YouTube Convert, Online YouTube Converter, YouTube to MP4, YouTube to AVI, YouTube to MP3, YouTube Download, YouTube Converter - Online-Downloader.com

Privacy Policy

Online Downloader Internet Privacy Policy

Online Downloader's Customer Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by Online Downloader anytime you interact with Online Downloader, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase Online Downloader products and services, or when you contact our sales or support associates. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at Online Downloader, and we go to great lengths to protect it. 

How we collect and use personal information 

Users accessing online video download and convert (Online-Downloader.com), we will collect the user's IP address, access time. Collect this information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's actions and favorite projects. We guarantee that your personal information will not be sold, but also will not associate IP addresses and personal information.

Collect your e-mail address 

Free users can not enter your email address online conversion. When the user is a registered user must enter your email address. Online file conversion (Online-Downloader.com) does not rent, sell, or share your personal information or e-mail address with any other company.

Some special cases 

If an individual user to convert users online threats and legitimate rights in the case of the website, your information is to be disclosed by the law of the license.

User file protection and storage policy 

When you convert a video to an online downloader(Online-Downloader.com) on the site, we will not back up any user files, and while the system is converted files will be automatically deleted after a successful upload. The new converted file will remain on the server for users to download, all files are automatically deleted after 24 after conversion, while the user can manually delete. We will not back up the users to convert files. It does not monitor the content of the file.

Security and Child Policy 

We are committed to ensuring the safety of your information while preventing unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place appropriate physical protection and procedural protection to ensure your personal information security. In order to protect children's safety, we do not knowingly collect personal information on marketing and children under the age of 13. When we know that information from children under the age of 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible.

Cookies and other technologies 

Online Downloader (Online-Downloader.com) site uses "Cookie" to store the information, we will only store personal online conversion preferences. We use third-party advertisers (Google Adsense). They use a "Cookie" technology to record the user is IP address and the user is browser, which is typically used for geotargeting purposes or expressed visited a particular website based on advertising goals.

Our companywide commitment to your privacy 

his policy covers the Intel Corporate website and is applicable worldwide. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to Online Downloader employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.
